# **Muhamad Aqil Naufal**

# **UI/UX Designer**

Tangerang | +62 852 1090 5222 | maqilnaufalb@gmail.com

#### **SUMMARY**

An ui/ux designer with 1+ years of experience in the design industry. Familiar with designing multiple prototypes using Figma and Adobe Xd. have worked on two ui/ux projects from a Bugar app a vaccination app and Cruzerverse a metaverse app in collaboration with my partner.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### PT SAYANG PEKERJA - Jakarta, Indonesia

Digital Marketing Executive (June 2020 - present)

- Lead the development of various digital marketing strategies such as engagement, sales conversion, and competitor analysis.
- Conceptualize and manage ad campaigns on Google with an average ROI of 20% for one year.
- Collaborate with teams from each department to ensure campaign strategies are aligned with business values and goals.

### PT KANTOR IMPIAN - Jakarta, Indonesia

Digital Marketing Officer (May 2017 - May 2020)

- Creating digital marketing campaigns for online channels like websites and social media.
- Using data from tools like Google Analytics to check the effectiveness of marketing campaigns.
- Tracking the success of campaigns and presenting the findings to management.

### **EDUCATION**

### UNIVERSITAS Multimedia Nusantara (2020 - present)

Bachelor of Information System - GPA 3.21

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

- Dicoding Academy (Cloud Practitioner Essentials 2021)
- Cisco Networking Academy (PCAP Programming Essentials in Python 2022)

### **SKILLS**

- Adobe Xd
- Figma
- Coreldraw

- Adobe Photoshop
- Microsoft Office